iolproperty.co.za 2019-03-24

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
THIS PRIVACY POLICY FORMS PART OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS
WEBSITE.
Click on the links below to access specific sections:
Definitions
Status and amendments
Collection of personal data
Collection of anonymous data
Access to personal data
Links to other web sites
Security
Children's privacy
Queries
Date of last review
Definitions
"personal information" is as defined in the Promotion of Access to Information Act No 2 of 2000
("PAIA")
"this website" means http://property.iol.co.za and www.iolproperty.co.za and all sub pages
thereof excluding links to external sites;
"user" means any person accessing any part of the web site
"web site owner" and/or "we" means Independent Online Property Joint Venture (Pty) Ltd
Status and Amendments
1. This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms and Conditions of Use of this web site. If you do
    not agree with this Policy then you may not use this website.
2. The website owner reserves the right to amend the terms and conditions of this Privacy
    Policy at any time. While the website owner will attempt to flag changes to this Policy as and
    when implemented, users remain at all times responsible for ensuring that they are aware of
    the current terms of this Policy whenever accessing this web site, and continued use of the
    site subsequent to any amendments having been effected constitutes users' acceptance of
    the Policy as amended.
Collection of personal data
3. Where personal information (such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address
    and credit card information) is submitted to the site by the user, for example through sending
    an e-mail or filling in required fields, the following principles are observed in the handling of
    that information:
             a. This website collects, processes and stores only such personal information
                 regarding users as is necessary to provide the services offered. The specific
                 purpose for which information is collected is apparent from the context in which it
                 is requested.

               b. This website will not use the personal information submitted for any other
                    purpose other than the efficient provision of services, including this web site and
                    services offered through it by third parties, without obtaining the prior written
                    approval of the user or unless required to do so by law.
               c. This website will keep records of all personal information collected and the
                    specific purpose for which it was collected for a period of one year from the date
                    on which it was last used.
               d. This website will not disclose any personal information regarding a user to any
                    third party unless the prior written agreement of the user is obtained or the
                    website is required or permitted to do so by law.
               e. If information is released with the user's consent this website will retain a record
                    of the information released, the third party to which it was released, the reason
                    for the release and the date of release, for a period of one year.
               f. This website will destroy or delete any personal information under its control
                    which has become obsolete.
4. Information collected about users through their use of this website is the property of the
    website owner.
5. The website owner will retain all ownership of and copyright in any database of users'
    personal information.
6. No credit card information is retained or stored by the website owner.
Collection of anonymous data
7. Note that, as permitted by the ECT Act, this website may use personal information collected
    to compile profiles for statistical purposes and trade in these profiles. No information
    contained in the profiles or statistics will be able to be linked to any specific user.
8. In order to provide the best possible and most relevant service, this website may use
    standard technology to collect information about the use of this site. This technology is not
    able to identify individual users but simply allows this website to collect statistics.
9. This website utilises cookies. A cookie is a small file that is placed on the user's hard drive in
    order to keep a record of a user's interaction with this website.
               a. Cookies from this website allow the website owner to tailor advertising and other
                    services to your displayed preferences. The website may use third party cookies
                    from an adserver for this purpose.
               b. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to personally identify users but will be
                    used to compile anonymised statistics relating to use of services offered or to
                    provide us with feedback on the performance of this website.
10. If a user does not wish cookies to be employed to customize his or her interaction with this
    website it is possible to alter the manner in which their browser handles cookies. Please note
    that, if this is done, certain services on this website may not be available.
Access to personal data
11. Where a user believes that personal data concerning them held by the web site owner is
    outdated or incorrect they may request that such personal data be corrected, please use our
    contact page http://www.iolproperty.co.za/Contact.jsp. Any request for such a correction must
    specify both the incorrect data and the proposed correction and must give full reasons for the
    request.

12. Users can request access to any relevant personal data held by the web site owner as laid
    out in the Promotion of Access to Information Act No 2 of 2000 ("PAIA") and where such
    access is necessary for them to exercise and/or protect any of their rights. A copy of PAIA
    can be obtained from http://www.polity.org.za/html/govdocs/legislation/2000/act2.pdf.
13. Detailed information on PROATIA and the procedure to follow in making a request for access
    to personal data is available in the web site owner's Promotion of Access to Information
    Manual and from the website of the Human Rights Commission www.hrc.org.za.
Links to other web sites
14. We have no control over and accept no responsibility for the privacy practices of any third
    party sites to which hyperlinks may have been provided and we strongly recommend that you
    review the privacy policy of any site you visit before using it further.
Security
15. While reasonable measures are taken to ensure the security and integrity of information
    submitted to this site, this web site can not under any circumstances be held liable for any
    loss or other damage sustained by a user or users as a result of the intentional or accidental
    release of information by an employee of the web site owner or any third party.
16. Users and/or subscribers are prohibited from releasing their username and/or password to
    any other person.
Children's privacy
17. We regard the safety and privacy of children using this web site extremely seriously but it
    remains the ultimate responsibility of the parents and other care-givers of children to ensure
    that they are not exposed to inappropriate content or behaviour.
Queries
18. If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy please contact as at
    http://www.iolproperty.co.za/Contact.jsp
Date of Last Review: 8 January 2009
prepared by ellipsis regulatory solutions © 2007, 2008. All rights reserved.
